foreign-trade.com 2016-03-13

# Privacy Statements - Foreign Trade Online

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Welcome to Foreign Trade Online! We have created this Privacy Statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our web site: foreign-trade.com. Our Privacy Statement is a work in progress. As we expand our services,we will update our Privacy Statement. We welcome your continuous input into this Privacy Statement. Give us your feedback at Administration. 

BY ACCEPTING THE TERMS OF SERVICE AGREEMENT ("AGREEMENT"), YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO OUR USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH OUR PRIVACY STATEMENT. OUR PRIVACY STATEMENT IS INCORPORATED INTO AND SUBJECT TO THE TERMS OF THE AGREEMENT. 

If you are not at least 18 years of age you are not eligible to use the Service,and we ask that you do not submit any personal information to us. 

**Member ID and Password.** When you register as a member, we require that you select a Member ID, and a Password. Your account is only accessible through the use of your Password. If you lose control of your Password, you may lose control over your personally identifiable information, and may be subject to legally binding actions entered into on your behalf. Therefore,if your Password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately contact us at Member Services. 

**Registration Information.** When you register as a member, we require that you fill out a registration form. The registration form requires that you provide your full name, street address, country, phone number and email address. In addition, you will be asked to provide your company's address, phone number, and a short description of your company's services or products. You are also provided with the option to fill out additional fields. These fields may include your company's city, province, zip code, facsimile number, home page, and your occupation. We use the registration information for gathering statistics on our membership. We will use these statistics to classify our members by, for example, age, industry and country, to target our registered members for new services and promotions. 

**Registration Information (Email).** We may use your email address to contact you regarding new services and promotions, including but not limited to monthly newsletters, offers and business opportunities from other users and partners of Foreign Trade Online. There is no opt-out email option as this is the only way of communication between FTO and among its members. You may un-subscribe at any time by sending an account removal request to Member Services. 

**Credit Cards.** Credit card processing is handled by a third-party company. We do not collect nor retain any credit card information. 

**Your Trading Activities.** We keep track of IP host addresses solely for security purposes only. We also keep track of total daily page views. The total daily page views are used to monitor traffic volume so that we can plan for our future growth (e.g.,more servers). 

**Advertising.** We may aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in aggregate to advertisers for marketing and promotional purposes. 

**Use of Cookies.** We use cookies to make our web site more "user friendly" by enabling you to use our services without having to repeatedly type in your registration information,and by tracking the status of your web browser. 

**Third Parties.** We post offers and business opportunities submitted by users and provide a mechanism by which other users may inquire about such offers and business opportunities. We do not give, sell, rent, share, or trade any identifiable personal information regarding our members to other third parties, with the exception of third party contractors and service providers who work with Foreign Trade Online to provide the web site and other services, and who are strictly prohibited from later use of the information that they may have access to. We will disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials when we believe in good faith the law requires it. 

**Storage and Transfer of Information.** Member information is collected and stored on servers in the United States. We may transfer, however, your information to other countries for backup purposes only. 

**External Links.** This site contains links to other sites. Foreign Trade Online is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We may at any time add business partners or co-branded sites, but the sharing of information with them will be limited to only aggregate information, and we will not disclose your identity. 

**Public Access to Trading Information.** The information that you provide to post an item for trade or to make an offer is posted in a public area, available to all users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security.** Our web site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These security measures include backing up data to other servers and encrypting user Passwords. Despite our security measures, please be advised that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

**Correcting Your Information.** You may change or update your personally identifiable information and Password (after a successful login process) through our web page at URL http://www.foreign-trade.com/members/logon.cfm 

**Contacting Us.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of Foreign Trade Online, or your dealings with the foreign-trade.com web site, you can contact us at Administration. 

Copyright © 1999-2016 Foreign Trade On-Line.  
All rights reserved.   **Privacy Statement**  
Please read important **copyright notices and disclaimers** information.
